Finding Aid for the Oliver Cromwell Carmichael Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Activities and organizations – Boards
  - Commission on Goals for Higher Education in the South
    - Strengthening and improving library resources (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - June – July 1961 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Reports, September 1961 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Map of North Carolina, 1962 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Graduate Education in the South – A Perspective; Improving Public Understanding of and Commitment to Higher Education (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Drafts of papers with revisions (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Papers - Improved Management in Higher Education; Improving the Faculty; Meeting the needs for public school teachers in the South (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Papers – Social Work Manpower needs in the South; Region’s need for College Trained Manpower; Research and Self Study as a Means of Improving Higher Education (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Papers, reports (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Paper – Within our Reach (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Papers on Admissions policies and Finance of higher education operations (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Commission on Goals for Higher Education in the South
    - Staff papers (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Staff papers (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Staff papers (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Staff papers (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Staff papers (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Staff papers (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Staff papers (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Rupert Vance paper (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Improving educational efficiency (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Staff papers (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Staff papers (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Reports and summaries (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Draft statement of areas discussed by commission, July 1961 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Staff papers (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Pamphlets and papers (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Danforth Commission on Church Colleges and Universities
    - Commission on Church Colleges and Universities – reports (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Commission on Church Colleges and Universities – reports (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - 1962–1965 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - 1963 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - 1963 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - 1963 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Case Study, 1963 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Case Study, 1963 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - 1964 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - 1965 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - 1965 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Case Studies (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Report on Church Sponsored Higher Education in the U.S. (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Hall of Fame for Great Americans at New York University
    - Addams, Jane (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Davis, Jefferson (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Davis, Jefferson (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Davis, Jefferson (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Edison, Thomas Alva (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Finlay, Dr. Carlos J. (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Gallatin, Albert (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Harrison, Caroline Scott (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Hunt, Walter (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Jackson, General Thomas (Stonewall) (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Jackson, General Thomas (Stonewall) (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Jackson, General Thomas (Stonewall) (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Jackson, General Thomas (Stonewall) (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Kane, Elisha Kent (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Kane, Elisha Kent (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Key, Francis Scott (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Knapp, Seaman A. (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - MacDowell, Edward (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Stanton, Elizabeth Cady (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Hall of Fame for Great Americans at New York University
    - Thayer, Sylvanus (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Thayer, Sylvanus (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Thayer, Sylvanus (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Thayer, Sylvanus (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Wald, Lillian (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Wald, Lillian (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Welch, William Henry (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Wiley, Harvey W. (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Other Candidates (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Other Candidates (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Electors (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Electors (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Handbooks and Lists (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Handbooks (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Handbooks (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - North Carolina Board of Higher Education
    - Report on Testing Programs and practices in North Carolina High Schools, 1955-56 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Reports, 1955–1957 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - August 17, 1957 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - September 1957 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - October 1957 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - November 1957 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - December 1957 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - January 1958 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - February 1958 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - March 1958 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - April – May 1958 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Report May 1958 (1) (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Report May 1958 (2) (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Report May 1958 (3) (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Report May 1958 (4) (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Report May 1958 (5) (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - June 1958 (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - September – November 1958 (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - December 1958 (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - 1958 (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - 1958 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - North Carolina Board of Higher Education
    - January 1959 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - February 1 – 4, 1959 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - February 5, 1959 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - February 9, 1959 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - February 11 – 28, 1959 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - March 1959 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - April 1959 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - May 1959 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - June 1 -10, 1959 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - June 10-30, 1959 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - July 1959 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - August 1959 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - September 1959 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - October 1959 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - November 1959 (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - December 1959 (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - January 1960 (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - February 1960 (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - March 1960 (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - North Carolina Board of Higher Education
    - April 1960 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - April 29 -30, 1960 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - May 1960 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - June 1960 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - July 1960 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - August 1960 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - September 1 -14,1960 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - September 15 – 30, 1960 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - October 1960 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - November 1960 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - December 1960 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - N.d./misc., 1960 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - N.d./misc., 1960 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - January 1961 (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - February 1 -15, 1961 (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - February 15 -28, 1961 (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - March 1961 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - April 1961 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - North Carolina Board of Higher Education
    - April 1961 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - May 1961 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - June 1961 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - July 1961 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - August 1961 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - September 1961 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - October 1961 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Novemer 1961 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - December 1961 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - 1961 – n.d (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Biennial Report, 1961-1963 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - January 1962 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - February 1962 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - March 1962 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - April 1962 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - May 1962 (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - June 1962 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - North Carolina Board of Higher Education
    - July 1962 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - August 1 – 20, 1962 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - August 21 – 31, 1962 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - September 1 -12, 1962 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - September 12 – 30, 1962 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - October 1962 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - November 1962 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - December 1962 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - 1962 – n.d (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - 1962 – n.d (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - January 1963 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - February 1 – 22, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - February 22 – 28, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - March 1963 (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - April 1 – 16, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - April 16 -30, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - North Carolina Board of Higher Education
    - May 1963 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - June 1963 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - July 1963 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - August 1963 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - September 1 -20, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - September 20 - 30, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - October 1 -18, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - October 18 -31, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - November 1 – 16, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - November 16 -30, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - December 1 -31, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - December 1963 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - 1963 – n.d (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - 1963 – n.d (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - 1963 – n.d (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - 1963 – n.d (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - 1963 – n.d (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - North Carolina Board of Higher Education
    - 1963 – n.d (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - January 1 -17, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - January 17 -31, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - February 1 -28, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - February 28, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - March 1964 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - April 1 -9, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - April 10 – 17, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - April 17 – 30, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - May 1964 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - June 1964 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - July 1964 (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - August 1964 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - North Carolina Board of Higher Education
    - September/October 1964 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - 1964 – n.d (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - January 1965 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 1965 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 1965–1970 – reports (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 1966 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - North Carolina Portrait Index, 1700–1860 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - School of Textiles, North Carolina State College, n.d (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Undated materials. (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Undated materials (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Undated materials (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Undated materials (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Undated materials (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Undated materials (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Undated materials (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Undated materials (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Nutrition Foundation Board of Trustees
    - 1942–1953 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 1953 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - 1953 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - January – April 1954 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - May – July 1954 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - August – October 1954 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - November – December 1954 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - January – February 1955 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - March – May 1955 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - June – August 1955 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - September – October 1955 (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - November – December 1955 (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - January – February 1956 (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - March – May 1956 (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - June – August 1956 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Nutrition Foundation Board of Trustees
    - September – December 1956 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - January – June 1957 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - July – December 1957 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - 1958 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - January – June 1959 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - July – December 1959 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - January – June 1960 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - July – September 1960 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - October 1960 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - November – December 1960 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - 1961 (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - undated (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Rollins College Board of Trustees
    - Programs, publications, bulletins, 1951–1964 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Statement of principles, Faculty By-Laws, May 31, 1955 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Data and Tables, 1955-1975 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - 1959 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - 1959 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - 1959 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Founder’s Day Convocation, award to OCC, February 23, 1959 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Minutes of the Faculty, 1958–1966 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - 1960 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - 1960 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - President’s Annual Report, February 1960 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Faculty and Faculty By-Laws, 1960 (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Alumni Report, 1960 (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - January – May 1961 (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - August – December 1961 (Box 83, Folder 15)
    - President’s Annual Report, February 1961 (Box 83, Folder 16)
    - 1962 (Box 83, Folder 17)
    - 1962 (Box 83, Folder 18)
    - President Hugh F. McKean’s Annual Report, 1962 (Box 83, Folder 19)
    - Report by Hugh McKean, 1962 (Box 83, Folder 20)
    - Memoranda from President McKean, 1962 (Box 83, Folder 21)
    - Report of the Visiting Committee, October 1962 (Box 83, Folder 22)
    - 1963 (Box 83, Folder 23)
    - 1963 (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - Rollins College Board of Trustees
    - 1963 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Report on the Library of Rollins College, 1963 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - President’s Annual Report, February 1963 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Centennial Commission, February 1963 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Report of the Dean of the College, 1963 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Report - Crummer School of Finance and Business, September 1963 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Report on Development Program, November 1963 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Report – Faculty Evaluation, 1963 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Centennial Commission, 1963–1965 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - 1964 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - 1964 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - 1964 (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - Report of the State of the College by President Hugh F. McKean – December 1, 1964 with newspaper clippings (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - 1965 (Box 84, Folder 15)
    - 1965 (Box 84, Folder 16)
    - 1965 (Box 84, Folder 17)
    - 1965 (Box 84, Folder 18)
    - Report of the Dean, February 1965 (Box 84, Folder 19)
    - Report of the President Hugh McKean, June 1965 (Box 84, Folder 20)
    - Report of the Alumni Association to the Trustees, June 1965 (Box 84, Folder 21)
    - Report Synoptic Course Project (Box 84, Folder 22)
- Activities and organizations - Boards
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools
    - Southern Association Reporter, 1953-1957 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Annual meeting, December 1954 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Annual report, 1954-1955 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Annual report – summer conference, June 1955 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Annual meeting, December 1955 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Reports, 1953–1956 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Budget report, 1955–1956 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Meeting minutes and other reports, 1956 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Summer conference, June 1956 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Summer conference – proposed study, June 1956 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Preamble, 1956 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Annual meeting, December 1956 (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Reports, 1956 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - Research proposal, February 1957 (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Summer conference, June 1957 (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - Meeting papers, 1957 (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools
    - Annual meeting, December 1957 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Budget, 1957–1958 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, January 1959 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Summer conference, June 1959 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Report, June 1959 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Manual for the Institutional Self – Study, 1959 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Manual for the Institutional Self – Study and related papers, 1959 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - 1961–1964 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - Proceedings Newsletter, 1965 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - (more room in this box), 1965 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Southern Regional Education Board
    - Prospectus and other material, 1957-1958 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Meetings, March 1958 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, November 1958 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - 1959 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Conference and other material, 1960 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Report of the Conference on Higher Education, 1961 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Case study; Panel Presentation, March 1961 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Meeting paper, March 1961 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Commission on Goals, 1961 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Meetings/agendas, 1961 (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Proposals/meetings, 1962 (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Georgia Alumni Record, 1962 (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - 1963-1965 (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Proposal for a Cooperative Program, Appendices A,B, C.,D (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - Biographical information on board members (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - Commission reports (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - North Carolina participation report (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - United States Department of State
    - International Educational Exchange Programs, 1953 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - International Educational Exchange Programs, 1953-1954 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Message from the President, March 1953; April 1954 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - International Educational Exchange programs, 1954 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - International Educational Exchange Programs, 1954 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - International Educational Exchange Programs, 1954-55 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - International Educational Exchange Service, 1955 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - International Educational Exchange, 1955 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - International Educational Exchange, 1955-1956 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Congressional Record, July 1955 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Educational Annual Reports, 1954-1957 (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - International Educational Exchange Proposal by J.L. Morrill, May 1956 (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Report by Paul Garner, 1960 (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - 1960-1965 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Affiliations - other organizations and institutions
    - Academy for Educational Development – Report, October 1964 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Agricultural and Technical College of North Carolina (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Alderson – Broaddus College, West Virginia – Bulletin, 1962-1964 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Alderson – Broaddus College, 1962 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Alderson – Broaddus College, 1962 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Alderson – Broaddus College, 1962 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Alderson – Broaddus College, 1962 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Alderson – Broaddus College - Reports, 1963 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Alderson – Broaddus College – Correspondence re: 1963 study (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Alderson – Broaddus College, 1963 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - American Association of Land – Grant Colleges and Universities, 1956-1958 (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - American Library Association – Bulletin, April 1953 (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - American Medical Colleges (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - American Medical Colleges (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - Affiliations – other organizations and institutions
    - American Medical Colleges (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - American Relief Administration, 1952 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Arizona Universities (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Arizona Medical School – study (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Arizona State University (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Asheville – Biltmore College (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Asheville, North Carolina (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Asia Foundation; Association for Asian Studies (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Asia Society, 1961–1962 (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Associates Investment Company of South Bend, Indiana – Report, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Association of Governing Boards (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Association for General and Liberal Studies (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - Association for Higher Education – National Conference, March 1960 (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Association for Higher Education, 1960 (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Association for Higher Education, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - Association for Higher Education, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - Affiliations – other organizations and institutions
    - Association for Higher Education – National Conference, March 1962 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Association for Higher Education – National Conference, March 1962 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Association for Higher Education, 1963 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Association for Higher Education, 1964 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Association of Graduate Schools (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Association of State Colleges and Universities (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Association of State Universities and Land – Grant Colleges (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Association of Universities of the British Commonwealth – report (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Association of Urban Universities, 1957 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Atlantic Council, 1961–1965 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Belgian American Educational Foundation, 1958-1959 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Belgian American Educational Foundation, 1960 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Belgian American Educational Foundation, 1962-1963 (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Belgian American Educational Foundation, 1964 (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - Belgian American Educational Foundation, 1964 (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Belgian American Educational Foundation, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - Affiliations – other organizations and institutions
    - Belgian American Educational Foundation, 1965 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Belgian American Educational Foundation, 1965-1966 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Birmingham Historical Society – Genealogy chart template (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Borden Company Foundation – awards (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Brazil Universities (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Brazil Universities (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Brazil Universities – University of Recife (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Brazil Universities – Catholic University, Rio de Janeiro (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Brown University, Rhode Island (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Bucknell University – Pennsylvania (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - California State College at Palos Verdes (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Canadian Universities (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Carthage College - Illinois (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - Century Association (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - Church Colleges (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - Cleveland Commission on Higher Education (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - College of St. Teresa – Minnesota (Box 92, Folder 17)
    - College of William and Mary – Virginia- Alumni Gazette, March 1943 (Box 92, Folder 18)
  - Affiliations – other organizations and institutions
    - Columbia Theological Seminary – Survey Committee (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Columbia Theological Seminary – Survey Committee (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Columbia Theological Seminary – Survey Committee – Reports (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Columbia Theological Seminary – Survey Committee – Reports (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Columbia Theological Seminary – Survey Committee - Reports (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Columbia Theological Seminary – Curriculum (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Columbia University (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Commission on the Education of Women (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Commission on the Education of Women – Papers and reports (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Commission on the Education of Women – Papers and reports (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Committee for Economic Development (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Commonwealth Club of California (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania – Department of public instruction (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Conference Board of Associated Research Councils (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Congress of Racial Equality (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - Continental Classroom (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - Continental Classroom (Box 93, Folder 17)
  - Affiliations – other organizations and institutions
    - Continental Classroom, 1959 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Continental Classroom, 1959 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Continental Classroom, 1959 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Continental Classroom, 1959 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Converse College – Oliver C. Carmichael, Jr. (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Co-Ordinating Council for Higher Education in California (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Council for the Advancement of Small Colleges (Box 94, Folder 7)